Jonathan Martin 6685 Woodbury Loop Morgantown, KY 42261 Email: contact@jamesjonathanmartin.com (preferred)

Phone: (270) 999-4625 (Please leave voicemail)

Website: jamesjonathanmartin.com

I was the coordinator of math tutoring, head math tutor, and an adjunct math and CIT/programming instructor at my local community college for seven years. I also have an additional six years of experience privately tutoring math since.

I am seeking a position as a remote math tutor.

EDUCATION

Louisville, KY	University of Louisville	2013 - 2015
M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE		
Bowling Green, KY	KCTCS & WKU	2010 - 2012
CS MASTER'S PREREQUISITES		
Bowling Green, KY	Western Kentucky University	2004 - 2009

B.S. IN MIDDLE GRADES EDUCATION, MATH AND SCIENCE

WORK HISTORY

PRIVATE MATH TUTOR 2017 - 2023 SUBSTITUTE TEACHER &

MARTIN ELECTRONICS CO-OWNER

- Privately tutored in primarily math, other subjects occasionally
- Taught as a substitute teacher for the local school system
- PC/Laptop troubleshooting and repair, PC System building, home network installation
- Collins Distribution Internet Reseller, OTA antenna sales and installation, satellite dish installation
- Home security system sales and installation, TV mount installation, MIMO cellular antenna installation

COORDINATOR OF MATH TUTORING INSTRUCTIONAL SPECIALIST & ADJUNCT INSTRUCTOR

SOUTHCENTRAL KY COMMUNITY AND TECHNICAL COLLEGE

2009 - 2016

- Tutored and coordinated tutoring in primarily math, other subjects occasionally
- Interviewed and trained student/part-time tutors
- Taught over 100 credit hours of math and CIT/programming courses, both online and in-person
- Award: The Learning Center at SKYCTC voted BEST Academic Improvement Program/Tutoring Center in area (2013)
- Award: SKYCTC Mentor Award Winner for exceptional service to students (2011)